Association of Canadian Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Chronological files, 1974 - 1981; F-57-6; 63 cm of textual records
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-66)
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-66)
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-66)
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-66)
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-66)
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-67)
  - Chronological files, 1980; F-57-6-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-67)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-67)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-67)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-67)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-67)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-68)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-68)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-68)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-68)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-68)
  - Chronological files, 1981; F-57-6-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-68)
- Briefs, 1961 - 1978; F-57-7; 49 cm of textual records; Dates: 1961, 1966, 1970-1976.
  Series consists of a collection of briefs to government relevant to the book publishing industry. Included are briefs from the Canadian Book Publishers Council and from the interim Council of Canadian Publishers, briefs to the Ontario Royal Commission on Book Publishing, miscellaneous briefs and speeches, briefs on copyright and libraries, IPA briefs and related correspondence, clippings and notes.
  - Submission to the Ontario Commission on Post-Secondary Education (CBPC), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to the Minister of National Revenue (C.C.P.), 1970; F-57-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Broad Policy Recommendations (CCP), F-57-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Book Publishing in Canada (CBPC), F-57-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Submission to Cabinet - Interim and Final Reports (Ontario Royal Commission on Book Publishing), 1973; F-57-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (Quill and Quire), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Study of Book Trade in Canada (Quill and Quire), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (Stroud, Bridgeman), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (Toronto Graphic Arts), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (United Church), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (York School Libraries), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (Queen's U.P.), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (Oxford UP), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission on Book Publishing (Robert Page), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (Peter Martin), F-57-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (Progress Books), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (MacLean-Hunter), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (MacMillan Co.), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Van Nostrand), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Gage), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Prentice Hall), F-57-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (MacLean-Hunter), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Festival Editions), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-69)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Burns and MacEachern), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Canadian Authors), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (Canadian Booksellers), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (Canadian Historical R), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Doubleday), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Clark, Irwin), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (General Publishing et al), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Griffen Press), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Wm. C. Heine), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (House of Anansi), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (CBPC), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (S.C.M. Book Room), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Toronto Public Library), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (Carswell Co. Ltd.), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (OISE, Saannes, W.G. Vine), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Submission to Royal Commission (O.C.U.L), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Brief to Royal Commission (OTF), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Rapport sur la distribution des periodiques, 1973; F-57-7-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Le Livre Canadien-Francais ... (AECB), 1973; F-57-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - How do all the Pieces Fit, Robin Farr, 1975; F-57-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Broadcasting and Publishing, Peter S. Grant, 1976; F-57-7-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - East Lookes West and South, Russell Hunt, 1973; F-57-7-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Politics of Publishing, James Lorimer, 1975; F-57-7-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Report of the Royal Commission on Publications, 1961; F-57-7-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-70)
  - Consultation 2: Publishing Workshop, 1971; F-57-7-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Brief to Economic Council (CCI), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Brief to Ontario Royal Commission (CCI), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Brief to the Bureau of Intellectual Property (CCI), 1974; F-57-7-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Brief to the Interdepartmental Committee - on Copyright, 1970; F-57-7-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Broadcasting and Cinematography, F-57-7-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - CCI Briefs re photocopying, 1970; F-57-7-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Compulsory Licenses in the Canadian Copyright Act (CCI), F-57-7-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - CCI Briefs re: U.S. Manufacturing Clause, 1966; F-57-7-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Brief to the Canadian Computer / Communications Task Force (CBPC and CCI), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Some Copyright Concerns (Roy Sharp), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Right of Reproduction and Untitled Brief (CCI), 1971; F-57-7-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Submission for a Grant (CCI), 1972; F-57-7-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Policy on Canadian Materials (Toronto Public Library), 1974 - 1975; F-57-7-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-71)
  - Canadian Juvenile Fiction (J.P. Wilkinson), 1975; F-57-7-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - The Impact of the Montreal Book Fair (IPA), 1974; F-57-7-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Development of Book Publishing in B.C. (and papers) (BCPG), 1974 - 1975; F-57-7-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Time magazine coverage of Canadian Books (clippings and correspondence), 1974; F-57-7-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Report on English Language Book Publishing (and responses) (IPA), 1974; F-57-7-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Ernst and Ernst Reports - notes, 1974; F-57-7-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Federal Publishing Policy: A Response (BPDC), 1975; F-57-7-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Brief Presented to Pat McGeer (BCPG), 1976; F-57-7-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Brief to Deputy Ministers of Education - Atlantic Publishers, 1977; F-57-7-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
  - Development and Use of Englsih Language Canadian Books (ACP), 1978; F-57-7-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-72)
- Newsletter, 1973 - 1982; F-57-8; 25 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the IPA Newsletter, (1973-77), Notebook (1977-82) and the Publishing Policy File (1980-81). The series is missing numbers 2, 3, 12 and 14 of the Notebook. Included are correspondence, clippings, photographs, and news releases that were used to compile the newsletter and the 1982 newsletter mailing list.
  - IPA/ACP Newsletter Vol. 1 No.1- Vol. 5 No.1, 1973 - 1977; F-57-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - Photographs, graphs, correspondence, 1974; F-57-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - Originals, correspondence, 1975; F-57-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - Original working file, 1975 - 1976; F-57-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - Original working file, 1976; F-57-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - Original working file, 1976; F-57-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - Original working file, 1976; F-57-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - ACP Notebook No. 1-16 (Missing Nos. 2,3,12,14), 1977 - 1978; F-57-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - ACP Notebook Vol. 2-3 No.3, 1979 - 1980; F-57-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - ACP Notebook Vol. 3 No. 3 - Vol. 5 No.1, 1980 - 1982; F-57-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-73)
  - ACP Notebook correspondence and papers, 1976 - 1980; F-57-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - ACP Notebook Mailing List, 1982; F-57-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1980; F-57-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1980; F-57-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1980; F-57-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1980; F-57-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1981; F-57-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1981; F-57-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook working file, 1982; F-57-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Notebook unfiled material - newsletters, correspondence, 1981; F-57-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - Publishing Policy File, Vol. 1 and 2, 1980 - 1981; F-57-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
  - PPF - correspondence, clippings, papers, 1980 - 1981; F-57-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-74)
- Members services, 1976 - 1984; F-57-9; 1.14 m of textual records 7 photographs; Physical description: 4 photographs found in F-57-9-2-29 Physical description: 2 photographs found in F-57-9-2-32 Physical description: 1 photograph found in F-57-9-2-33
  Series consists of records relating to the ACP's program of professional development and foreign fairs assistance to its members.
  - Professional development, 1977 - 1983; F-57-9-1; 54 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records relating to professional development. Included are minutes and papers of the Professional Development Committee (1977-79), correspondence, reports, transcripts, programs, brochures and catalogues relating to professional development seminars organized by the ACP and other organizations. The seminars covered financial, technical, legal and marketing aspects of book publishing. Funding assistance was provided by the Secretary of State.
    Arranged chronologically by seminar.
    - Professional Development Committee - Minutes and Papers, 1977; F-57-9-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Production Seminar, 1977; F-57-9-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Seminar on Agencies and Rights - correspondence, 1977; F-57-9-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Seminar on Agencies and Rights - papers, 1977; F-57-9-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Professional Development Committee - Minutes and Papers, 1978 - 1979; F-57-9-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - French/English Publishing Seminar, 1977 - 1978; F-57-9-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Conference on the Canadian Novel, 1978; F-57-9-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - The British Mission - Seminar proceedings, 1978; F-57-9-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Ele-hi Education Marketing Seminar, 1977 - 1978; F-57-9-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Ele-hi Education Marketing Seminar, 1978; F-57-9-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-75)
    - Modes of Publishing Seminar - Correspondence, transcript, 1978; F-57-9-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Production Seminar (never held), 1979; F-57-9-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Bookings for Seminars - correspondence, 1979; F-57-9-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Professional Development Survey, 1979; F-57-9-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Alternatives in Marketing - corresponcence and papers, 1979; F-57-9-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Alternatives in Marketing - transcript, 1979; F-57-9-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Marketing and Government Assistance to Publishers (APA), 1979; F-57-9-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Seminar on Children's Book Publishing, 1979; F-57-9-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Seminar on Children's Book Publishing - Transcript, 1979; F-57-9-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - General Correspondence, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Canada Council Correspondence, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Secretary of State Correspondence, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - International Credit Seminar (CBPC), 1980; F-57-9-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Contracts and Rights (ACP and ABPBC), 1980; F-57-9-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-76)
    - Subsidiary Rights Seminar (ACCP/CBPC), 1980; F-57-9-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - How to Create Books that Sell (ABPBC), 1980; F-57-9-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Book Design and Manufacturing Seminar (APA), 1980; F-57-9-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Colour Reproduction in Children's Books - Correspondence, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Colour Reproduction in Children's Books - Registration, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Colour Reproduction in Children's Books - Transcript, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Books and Broadcasting - correspondence, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Books and Broadcasting - Transcript, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Courses, other countries - catalogues, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - Courses, other countries - catalogues, 1980; F-57-9-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-77)
    - General Correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Brochure, 1981; F-57-9-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Finance for the Non-Financial - correspondence and papers, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Finance for the Non-Financial - Toronto Registration, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Finance for the Non-Financial - Vancouver Registration, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Marketing Seminar (SPG), 1981; F-57-9-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Distribution Task Force Seminar, 1981; F-57-9-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Binding Operation (with CBPC), 1981; F-57-9-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Marketing and Costing for Small Press Books, 1981; F-57-9-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Computer Communications Systems and Publishing, 1981; F-57-9-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Book Publishers Professional Associate Seminars, 1979 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Canadian Management Centre, 1981; F-57-9-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Freelance Editors Association Seminars, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Recommended courses - prospectus, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-78)
    - Recommended courses, 1981; F-57-9-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Children's Editors Apprenticeship Program, 1980 - 1982; F-57-9-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Book Publishers Development Council, 1982; F-57-9-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Brochure, 1982 - 1983; F-57-9-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Folio Publishing Co. Seminars, NY, 1982 - 1983; F-57-9-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
  - Foreign fairs, 1976 - 1984; F-57-9-2; 60 cm of textual records 7 photographs
    Subseries consists of records relating to ACP and Canadian publishers attendance and book displays at major international book fairs such as London, Frankfurt and Bologna. Included are correspondence, memoranda, telegrams, lists, notes, clippings, business cards, brochures, programs, floor plans and photographs.
    Follows original order of annualized files, and alphabetically by fair.
    - American Booksellers' Association Exhibit, 1976; F-57-9-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1976 - 1977; F-57-9-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - London Book Fair, 1976; F-57-9-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - American Booksellers' Association Convention, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - American Library Association Conference, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1976 - 1977; F-57-9-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Commonwealth Book Fair, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Learned Societies Conference, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - London Book Fair, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Moscow Book Fair, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Warsaw International Book, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Washingtonian Book Festival, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - American Booksellers' Association Convention, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - American Library Association Exhibition, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1977; F-57-9-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Canadian Booksellers' Association, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - London Book Fair, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-79)
    - Montreal International Book Fair, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - Warsaw Book Fair, 1978; F-57-9-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - American Booksellers' Association Convention, 1978 - 1979; F-57-9-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1979; F-57-9-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1979; F-57-9-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - London Book Fair, 1978 - 1979; F-57-9-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - Moscow Book Fair, 1979; F-57-9-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - Foreign Fairs Questionnaire, 1980; F-57-9-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - American Booksellers' Association Convention, 1979 - 1980; F-57-9-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-80)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1979 - 1980; F-57-9-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1979 - 1981; F-57-9-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1980; F-57-9-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - London Book Fair, 1979 - 1980; F-57-9-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - London Book Fair - catalogue, photograph, 1980; F-57-9-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - London / Frankfurt - ACP delegate, 1980; F-57-9-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - London / Frankfurt - follow-up, 1980; F-57-9-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - International Books Fairs, 1979 - 1980; F-57-9-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - Foreign Fairs Survey, 1981; F-57-9-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-81)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1980 - 1981; F-57-9-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1981; F-57-9-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1981; F-57-9-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - London Book Fair, 1981; F-57-9-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Salon du Livre, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - General, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Foreign Fairs Survey of Publishers, 1982; F-57-9-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Exporting Canadian Books, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - American Booksellers' Association Convention, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-82)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1982; F-57-9-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - London Book Fair, 1981 - 1982; F-57-9-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Foreign Fairs General, 1981 - 1983; F-57-9-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - American Booksellers' Association Convention, 1982 - 1983; F-57-9-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1983 - 1984; F-57-9-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Leipzig '82 Design Awards - ACP Reception, 1983; F-57-9-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - London Book Fair, 1982 - 1983; F-57-9-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Foreign Fairs General, 1983 - 1984; F-57-9-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Bologna Children's Book Fair, 1983 - 1984; F-57-9-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1983 - 1984; F-57-9-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
    - Trade Mission to Mexico, 1982 - 1984; F-57-9-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-83)
- Literary Press Group, 1975 - 1982; F-57-10; 89 cm of textual records